WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
We're almost at
the Village Hidden in the Leaves.
Is everybody here?
— Yes, sir!
Big Brother Omasa,
we're missing one!
What? Who is it?!
It's Idate! Morino Idate!
damn, he's such a hopeless kid!
What should we do?
Shall we wait?
We have no choice...
What the...?!
Who is it?!
You people are from the Wasabi Family
of the Land of Tea, correct?
Who are you!
You should know your place.
Hooligans like you people
are no match for a Shinobi!
Please don't worry.
I won't take your lives.
If you've learned from this,
you should give up the race
at Todoroki Great Shrine.
Blast it!
I have to at least deliver this letter
to the Hidden Leaf Village.
OK! Mission! Mission!
I'm so eager to do it!
But Kakashi-sensei is not here.
Is he late as usual?
No, Kakashi will not be coming.
It's Grandma Tsunade!
Don't call me an old lady!
Excuse me... Hokage-sama...
What do you mean by
Kakashi-sensei will not be coming?
As you three already know,
most of the Jonin including Kakashi
are on different missions.
This time, the three of you will have
to execute the mission by yourselves.
This is a B-rank mission,
escorting an important figure!
Escorting an important figure...
Of course,
depending on the situation,
the mission has the possibility
of becoming an A-rank.
And, who are we protecting?
Don't know...
What do you mean
"don't know"?!
In the neighbouring nation
of the Land of Tea,
they have a Dedication Ceremony
at the Todoroki Great Shrine
once every four years.
We've received a request
to escort the runner
who will be participating in
the race that will be held there.
But an assailant from the opponent's side
attacked the messengers
before they arrived here.
Assailant?
Excuse me, but I still don't
quite understand the mission.
Well, you should get the details
directly from Boss Jirocho.
Boss Jirocho?! Oh yeah!
The boss from that time!
That's it.
Now that you three understand,
depart immediately!
Get to the Land of Tea by today.
Snap to it!
— Yes!
— All right.
Okay!
Roger that!
I'm counting on you.
Come Now,
New Mission
Save the Obligation,
The Sympathy and the
Country of Tea!
Hey Sakura, aren't you hungry?
Well, a little bit...
Then it's decided!
And perfect timing!
There's a tea-house right over there!
Hey, Naruto.
You're here...?
Rokusho Aoi has now arrived.
I had you go through
all that trouble,
but Jirocho of the Wasabi
does not know when to give up.
Is he still trying to take part
in the race at Todoroki Great Shrine?
That's right.
And there's new information
that they have also hired Shinobi.
I see...
Then next time, let's beat them
to a pulp at the race...
Welcome!
Ma'am, I'll have sweet bean soup.
Then I'll have dumplings.
How about you, Sasuke?
Jelly...
All right, please wait for a moment.
Ninja from the Leaf...
I'm gonna work so hard!
Naruto, don't take unnecessary action
by yourself.
Oh, okay.
Having sweet bean soup
when it's so nice outside.
The Ninja profession sure
is carefree!
What did you say?
Things must really be peaceful
for the Leaf Village.
Such a dense-looking
bunch of guys...
What?!
Hey! I didn't know there was
such a cutie here.
I take back that previous comment!
Ah... pardon me.
I'm Idate Morino.
What's your name, young lady?
Don't you talk to Sakura
in such a familiar tone!
Sakura... That's a good name.
Hey, even a chance meeting is due
to karma from a previous life.
Why don't we talk about our future?
Huh? Talk about... the future?
I'm talking about you quitting
the Ninja life and becoming my bride...
Hey you! How dare you
hit on her all of a sudden!
Don't be silly!
Just joking.
But hey, you fool!
Idate here hates Ninja!
If you wander around
the Land of Tea anymore,
there'll be a price to pay!
That's amusing! Bring it on!
Hey, Naruto!
Ridiculous! We don't have time
to waste on a hooligan.
Be quiet, Sasuke!
I'm not going to forgive a guy
who makes fun of Shinobi!
I'm going to punish this guy...
Huh?
He's gone...
Impossible!
I didn't even notice...
Where did that guy run away to?!
Here, thank you for waiting.
Dang it!
Thank you for your patronage.
What? Two bills?
This is...?
Oh, that kid who was here left,
saying that you guys would pay.
That guy!
How dare he make fools of us!
The sound of footsteps is far off...
He has considerable speed!
He made us look like idiots!
I can't stay quiet.
We have to chase him!
Missus, thank you very much.
I'll leave the money here.
Thanks!
All the customers today
seem to be in such a hurry.
He has incredible speed.
He must have trained very hard.
Who is he?
Doesn't matter, we're definitely
going to catch up to him!
Stupid Ninja!
There's no way
they can catch up to me!
Owww!
damn it... Swift Runner Idate
makes a mistake of a lifetime!
Serves you right!
You have some nerve,
trying to run away from us.
I'm so sorry!
Huh?
I'm sorry...
I had my wallet stolen and was at a loss,
then you guys showed up.
So I did that...
You kinda feel sorry
after hearing his story.
Then you should have said that
from the start!
Ow! Huh...?
What's this?
Don't touch it!
This is mine!
Wh-What the...?!
On your mark.
Get set...
Go!
Weights?
Try to catch me now, you idiots!
Hey! He escaped again!
That guy!
He simply doesn't get it!
Is he for real?
What speed...!
No way!
Even we can't catch up to him...?
That's it. We don't have a chance
of catching up.
Dang it! He'll get it
when I see him next time!
All of you, thanks for coming.
Begging your pardon!
I was born and raised
in the Leaf Village in the Land of Fire.
I was bathed in birth water
at "Ichiraku Ramen."
My given name is Naruto
and the surname is Uzumaki.
People call me...
Loser!
Loser...? Nah, not that!
You're funny as usual.
Boss Jirocho,
you're looking good yourself.
Hey, Naruto!
That's okay.
A boy should be this spunky.
The greetings seem to be done,
so I'll get to the main topic.
The Fifth Hokage told us to get
the details of this mission from you.
Yes, in fact...
Do you know of the Dedication Ceremony
at the Todoroki Great Shrine?
To... Todo... what?
Well, make yourselves comfortable.
The legend goes...
A long time ago,
in order to subdue a storm,
Ryuko's Jewels were dedicated
to the Todoroki Great Shrine
and the storm subsided.
It became a customary event
that happens once every four years.
At first, it was just to dedicate the
jewels, but several decades ago,
it became a festival in which
the first-place runner
became the man of the year.
In recent years, the festival has
taken on another face.
For ages now,
in this port town of Degarashi,
two families,
the Wasabi and the Wagarashi,
have controlled local operations
and policed the town.
It's embarrassing,
but conflict between the two families
has never ceased and
there have been numerous skirmishes
over territorial rights.
As the struggle intensified,
the town residents became entangled
and even got injured...
In order to put a stop to the conflict,
for the first time,
there was talk of some kind of mediation
in the presence of the lord.
And it was agreed that the power holder
of the town
would be determined in a contest
rather than through brawls.
So that contest is...
It is the Todoroki Great Shrine
Dedication Ceremony
that is held every four years.
Four years ago, the Wagarashi
easily won by hiring a Shinobi,
and we have learned that
they've hired a Shinobi again this year.
In order to counteract that,
we sent messengers to
the Hidden Leaf Village with a request,
but they were ambushed and attacked.
I beg you guys!
Please lend us your power.
We cannot afford to lose this race
to the Wagarashi Family!
Leave it to me!
And, who do you want us
to escort?
Oh, so you'll take this job?
Did you call for me, Boss?
Oh, you guys know each other?
Then that makes the story fast.
That might not actually
be the case...
Boss Jirocho is an important person!
By rights, he shouldn't bow
his head to Ninja like you!
Even if he did bow his head,
I'd flatly refuse to escort a guy like you.
Oh yeah?!
As if I'd go with some guy who came
from who-knows-where!
"Some guy from who-knows-where"?!
I am the brilliant Ninja,
Uzumaki Naruto,
who will eventually inherit
the name of Hokage!
Hah! Hokage is no big deal!
Hah! The boss of hooligans
is even less of a big deal!
You idiot! Boss Jirocho is
a very honourable person!
The Hokage is a great Shinobi
who puts his life on the line
to protect the village!
Boss Jirocho is a very,
very, very honourable person
who always puts his life
on the line to protect the town!
Hokage is more, more,
more incredible!
Even though it's a tourist resort,
everything seems so expensive.
Sorry about that.
It sure is expensive, isn't it?
Oh no, I didn't mean...
We actually don't want to sell
at this kind of price,
but after the Wagarashi family
came into power...
P-Please forgive me!
How dare you?!
Do you know who you have
to thank to do business?
Are you actually thinking about turning
against the Wagarashi Family?
N-Not at all.
But I have to get paid...
You're slow to understand.
— Hey!
— Yes, sir!
P-Please stop!
Huh! First of all, we'll destroy you...
Wh-Who are you?!
Get out of here before you get hurt!
— What?!
Please run away!
These people are from
the Wagarashi...
It'll be fine.
— You punk!
— Wise guy!
We'll let you go for today!
If you've learned your lesson,
never defy us again, kid!
Or you'll pay when
we see you next time!
— Y-You won't get away with this!
Young man...
Thank you very much.
What a refreshing feeling!
We definitely need Boss Jirocho's
Wasabi Family to win the upcoming race.
Sasuke...
Yeah...
Boss...
Of all people,
did you have to ask the Leaf Shinobi?
Don't sulk like that, Idate.
I'm not sulking.
It's just that...
Idate...
I believe in you more
than anybody else.
The rest depends on you.
Why don't you believe
in people a little?
Idate...
please run for this town.
I beg you!
Boss...
Okay.
Even in exchange for my life...
Wow, I didn't think it was going
to be this big!
But what kind of race is it?
I'll explain the course so
a dummy like you can understand.
The starting point is Degarashi Port.
After the start, you head for
Modoroki Shrine which is the midway point.
This is Modoroki Shrine...?
Yes... It seems the fastest way
to get to Modoroki Shrine
is to use a boat from here.
Then you take one of two Ryuko's jewels
from Modoroki Shrine and
dedicate that jewel at the
Todoroki Great Shrine on Ouzu Island.
That's the only rule
for the race.
So shortcuts, obstructions,
and secret maneuvers are all allowed.
So hiring a Ninja is not
a violation of the rule either.
Who are the Ninja that
the other side hired?
They're hiding somewhere
and checking the situation.
Don't be careless, Naruto!
R-Right!
You guys can just relax and watch.
Don't follow me around!
What?!
I'm saying I don't want
an impediment.
You!
Calm down.
Let's join forces here.
— Not with a guy like this!
They seem to strangely be
in harmony, these two.
All right, everybody!
The Todoroki Great Shrine Race
will start soon!
Wasabi Family's runner,
Idate Morino!
Idate... Morino?
Wagarashi Family's runner,
Fukusuke Hikyakuya!
On your mark!
Start!
All right! We're going too!
Wh-What the...?!
Is he running away?!
Where are you going, Idate?!
Hey, wait!
Wh-What is he doing...?
Wait!
I BELIEVE YOUR PROMISE ITS TRUE HEART TO GIVE ME COURAGE
I believe your promise, it's a true heart gives me courage
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
tachidomatta kado ni
on your still shoulder
asu e mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
I feel the wind that blows towards tomorrow
machi no akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
the city lights are like pieces of stars
futari tsutsumu kedo
that hold us together
sorezore ni chigau kagayaki ga aru to
"each one of us glows differently"
warau kimi ga
you say laughingly
ichiban mabushiku mieru yo
but you look most dazzling
yume wa ryuusei no you ni
like a comet
ameagari no niji no you ni
like the rainbow after the storm
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
you bring light into my heart
nayami tsuzukeru koto ga hitotsu no kotae ni naruyo
being lost can be the answer
gomakashitari shinai to chikau no
let's promise we won't cheat
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
What the heck is he thinking?!
That idiot!
So fast. He's moving at
an incredible speed.
damn it! The opponent's already
far out at sea!
This is bad!
If the distance between them gets
any greater, it'll be impossible to win!
That idiot!
— Kick it up a notch, Sakura!
— Right!
We're gonna bring him back at all cost
and make up the difference!
Next time:
"The Race is On! Trouble on the High Seas!"
Don't miss it!